Save the best piece for last.
American Reunion is a comedy film directed by Jon Hurwitz.
The characters we met a little more than a decade ago return to
East Great Falls for their high school reunion.
In one long-overdue weekend, they will discover what has changed, who hasn’t,
and that time and distance can’t break the bonds of friendship.
Jim Levenstein, played by Jason Biggs.
Michelle Levenstein, played by Alyson Hannigan.
Steve Stifler, played by Seann William Scott.
Chris 'Oz' Ostreicher, played by Chris Klein.
Kevin Myers, played by Thomas Ian Nicholas.
Victoria 'Vicky' Lathum, played by Tara Reid.
American Reunion (also known as American Pie 4: Reunion or American Pie: Reunion in certain countries) is a
2012 American sex comedy film written and directed by Jon Hurwitz and Hayden Schlossberg.
It is the fourth and final installment in the American Pie theatrical series.
The film's ensemble cast features many actors who reprise their roles from the previous three films, including Jason Biggs, Alyson Hannigan,
Chris Klein, Thomas Ian Nicholas, Seann William Scott, Eddie Kaye Thomas, Eugene Levy, Tara Reid, and Mena Suvari, among others.
The film follows former East Great Falls High School classmates who return
to their hometown for a reunion for their graduating class.
Released in the United States on April 6, 2012 by Universal Pictures, American Reunion received generally mixed reviews
from critics, but was a worldwide box office success, grossing $235 million against a $50 million budget.
The film explores themes of husband wife relationship,
sequel, family reunion, masturbation, scat.
The tone is lighthearted.